a new future begins now
hello agents. I'm Susan Moyer and this is the Ingress report
three years ago, an artist known as Tyco interrupted a panel at comic-con in SanDiego
before being abducted by NIA operatives
the five images he left behind was the first window into the Niantic project and the world of Ingress
reports surfaced recently that Tyco is now preparing a new graphic novel
known as Ingress: origins which will shed even more light on many of the secrets
that remain at the heart of Niantic
at the Mission day in San Diego this past weekend
over five hundred agents joined together to explore the sights and sounds of the city
first night when I was here with Ingress
sat on a restaurant and someone looked over and saw my scanner and said
hey you need any items I have some extra items to give you
well either you play xbox you know sat on the couch all day
or play a game that you get to explore the city you live in
learn things you never knew about
New art from Tyco also emerged during the mission meet-up
following the Persepolis finale in Portland P.A.Chapeau was reported
he had been unable to make contact with Klue
someone concerned for the investigators' safety
after fears that Klue may have been forcibly abducted
or ADA may have attempted to once again infiltrate her mind
however at the mission Klue and PA were seen together interacting with agents
Intel emerged ADA had been tracking Klue very closely since their split
and may in fact be researching her to determine the effects of this separation
it seems that both PA and Klue were in San Diego while at the request of another party
by completing a series of missions
agents there assisted PA and Klue in retrieving a set of messages
the message said the following
both has the answer clue is the key
I will keep you updated the detail ** merge
in the last few weeks agents have undertaken a number of impressive missions
in the United States Southern California agents mark Independence Day July 4th
with a cross faction field up project called Operation: One Nation
over the course of 24 hours nearly sixty agents
organized by agents @4MadHatters @Viciouskitties @DIEdoll @PaTChBuZ006, @BBQOracle and @Splitends
helped build a large American flag
the flag spanned over 420 square kilometers when completed
in the Bordeaux region of France
enlightened agents undertook operation SOFA over 20 agents including
@StormOdd @Cataract  @Macgregor @TaRISTiAN @Clodomir and @lenalvida
took part in the creation of the massive enlightened eye
which spans over thirty five thousand kilometers when it was completed
and finally resistance agents in Europe and Asia
assisted in a massive operation Summer Breeze
an 11 layered field ops spending the Canary Islands to Norway in Kuwait
capturing over five and a half billion mind units in total
each of these giant fields was worth over 500 million MU alone
a new feature will be rolling out to Ingress agents across the world this week
Ingress on Android wear will enable agents to hack portals and collect XM using their smart watches
the new feature was reportedly created by the Japanese XM researcher Major Akira Tsukasa
who previously is known to have assisted SoftBank
in the development at the SoftBank Ultra Link
until next time continue to share your operations on Facebook and Google+ using the hashtag #Ingress
I look forward to covering your remarkable stories in the weeks to come
for the Ingress report I'm Susan Moyer
he will not stop me