What lies hidden in *geneva*?
Hello agents, I'm Susanna Moyer and this is the
Ingress report
Recently the Anti-Magnus leader Jahan
released a message expressing her vision
for the future,
and the path that she believes must be
traveled to achieve it.
In the video Jahan accuses the
enlighted activist known as the Acolyte
of deception and creating false hopes.
JARVIS, ahd this Acolyte whoever she might be.
Would have you bathed in the sun and dreamed of a better world
while your
fellow human beings are suffering.
It is believed Janan is attempting to activate N'zeer
technological artifacts
beneath the ancient city of Persepolis.
P. A. Chapeau and Hank Johnson
have recently commented on Jahan's activities.
After breaking the slience,
is it possible that her efforts began to
*bear freeps*?
Over the last few weeks, agents have been
gathering in large numbers to take part in Mission days.
On July 18 in Stuttgart, over four hundred
agents
from France, Switzerland, Italy, Germany, the USA,
Norway and the Czech Republic
met for a cross-faction breakfast followed by a day of exploration.
Using missions created in coordination with
the Stuttgart Tourism Authority,
agents explored this beautiful andhistoric city.
Just a few days later,
over two hundred agents met in Oslo for a cross-fraction
meet up and a mission date there.
And this Saturday,
on August 1st, a mission day will be
taking place in Indianapolis
at the site of Gen Con,
the gaming convention created by the father of
Dungeons and Dragons Gary Gygax.
In March of 2013,
A Gary Con in Lake Geneva, Wisconsin which
honors Gary Gyax.
Misty Hannah took advantage of an
anomaly held there
to escape from the Niantic project
facility at "Sern".
Two weeks ago agents at the Mission day
in San Diego comic-con
discovered valuable intel through a
series admissions connected to P.A. Chapeau and Klue
who were both present.
Given the potential importance of Gen
Con
I advise agents on the ground to be on the lookout for
intel emerging in missions there.
Please share anything you might discover
on Facebook & Google+.
As well as the mission day at Gen Con
agents around the world will be
gathering in over 100 cities
for agent-organized ingress First Saturday on August 1st.
Find more information about them on
Google+.
In Munich, enlighted agents from Austria and
Germany met in a botanical garden
to launch operation white unicorn,
a field art projects creating an emblem
from an anime series" Mobile Suit Gundam".
Over 40 agents were involved
including *fivegirl, Lord0pool, theparrot, and backtop*.
In Japan resistance agents *marked*
National Marine Day
by launching a field
art operation to create a parrot fish
in an area typically under enlightened
control.
In addition, the agents created a massive link burst
in the form of sea urchin to distract
their opposition and buy time.
24 agents were involved in the creation
of the field art
including blocco, kosira, BooBeeDoo and manchigo.
In Taiwan, enlightened agents launched operation Jade
creating a level 8 portal at the top of the main peak of
Mount Jade, the highest mountain in Taiwan,
a difficult mountain to access and
Summit.
The team had to plan their hike for over three months
and their details
sitrep is well worth read.
10 agents completed the hike
AuntieJiao, Breathfreeair, ChunLunKuan, GV4WKK3R, HuskyTsai,
JOSEPHlu7, lazica, LongVacation, n20hach and PetrCoder.
And on the 18th of July,
resistance agents from Hong Kong, Guangdong,
Henan and Hainan, launched operations summer swim,
a multi-tiered field operation started at 6 fields controlling 440,000 MU.
They then *added* two more layers and 2.5
million mind units.
Finally ending with two massive field
that controlled 54 million MU.
Nearly seventy agents were involved
including MonsterKL, monocolor, FireSteed,
CrowSnow and BindingLayer.
Later today,Agent Portalyst will be appearing on
Behind the SCANNER.
She's currently at Gen Con in Indianapolis
and claims to have discovered some
troubling intel from a portal there.
Tune into Behind the SCANNER tonight at
9:00 PM eastern time to learn more.
Thanks for joining me this week.
Continue to share your sitreps and the stories of
your communities around the world
on Facebook and Google+ using the hashtag #ingress
or leave a comment on the ingress Facebook page
to be feathered in next week's ingress report.
I look forward to seeing and sharing
your messages.
For the ingress reports i'm Susanna Moyer.
I can see every possibility.