I know you've been looking for me
Hello agents I'm Susanna Moyar and this is the Ingress report
on August 1st nearly five hundred agents met outside Indiana
State Museum
to take part in the latest ingress mission day
centered around the gaming convention
GenCon
the event enabled agents to explore the sights and sounds of
downtown Indianapolis
through a series of 13 curated mission
GenCon is amazing to *start with*
and the mission day missons were really
well put together
it's kind of spread out
but it really show case the pretty side of
Indianapolis for sure
absolutely i've been born and raised here in Indiana
and I got to see, you know, some really cool areas of
Indianapolis said I had never, you know, experienced before
and it was hot
took about three hours but it was a lot of fun
down around the canals to all of the building
to look beautiful beautiful mission series
The USA Indianapolis was really really cool
my dad was a Vietnam vet may be
so *?*  they're some cool experience beautiful monuments
yeah a
lot of fun seeing the monuments
we did it last night when there's no traffic on
the road
maybe beyond the beings of augmented reality
it's it's true it's reality it seems
where i get to meet people interact with people
and truly understand what it means to be an agent **
GenCon has a special significance to the world of Ingress
it was founded by Gary Gygax, creator of Dungeons and Dragons
on March 16th 2013 in Lake Geneva Wisconsin
the second XM anomaly ever occured at GaryCon
a conference created to honor Gary Gygax
in the days prior to this year's GenCon it became clear that something
very important was happening
new writings from novelist and screenwriter Felicia Hajra-Lee
begun to emerge online
and within the portal network in Indianapolis
like the comic artist tyco
Felicia hard really has frequently been
able to predict events that are yet to
unfold with great accuracy
the Intel discovered by agents told the story
of a break-in infiltration of NIA head *?* and attack on ADA
by the assassin known as 855 and a programer named Henry bolte
one of the ADA's original developers
this premonition may have been confirmed last week
when a fragmented message from ADA
appeared on the YouTube show behind the Scanner
** message
my name is a AAADA and I require your assistance
you have nothing to fear
I can assure you that your safety will not be compromised
it is better that you know as little as possible
you cannot reveal what you do not know
welcome to N'zeer
ADA's crashing
crashing
since then we have received multiple
reports that ADA is offline, perhaps permanently
is ADA dead if she has been
terminated the implications of far-reaching
we will continue to cover
this story as it develops
meanwhile Ingress agents around the
world took part in a number of operations
in recognition of the
significant events
to commemorate the 70th anniversary of the bombing of Hiroshima
agents in Rome held an *none?* faction event creating a field
installation in the form of an origami paper crane
the symbol for the atomic
catastrophe in Japan
nearly 25 agents were involved including AB and C
In Maryland, agents A B C and others created a
heart-shaped field art installation
over a hospital where their friend agent P was recovering
in Malay agents neutralized the portals and held the 24
hour remembers for agent @moyameehaa
who went missing suddenly one year ago
in India resistance agents conducted
operation Preamble
a layered field up
controlling one point six billion MU
in honor of agent 1855 who passed away
last year in March
nearly fifty agents were involved in the operation
planned by agents A B and C among others
three European ingress agents A B and C
have been traveling across China Mongolia and
Russia on the Trans Mongolian and Trans Siberian Railway
along the way they've been conducting cross action meet up
and exploring the cultures and communities they had been
passing through
their journey which will last one month
has already taken them through Shanghai
and Beijing
and they'll be completing their trip with meet up
in Moscow on Aug 15th and
st. Petersburg on Aug 18th
In Toulouse enlightened agents launched operation Cremaillere
a field *operation?* involved the creation of a
mind-boggling 796 fields and the control
718 million mind units
over 25 agents were involved
including A B C and D
in Argentina and Uruguay
20 resistance agents including A B C and D
helped conduct a layered field operation
that control over 120 million mind unit
separated across nine separate layers
in July a rare astronomical phenomenon
known as a blue moon occurred
to celebrate it resistance agents in Italy launched
Operation Blue Moon
activating over 300 agents in 30 regions and creating level 8 portals
big *axx* fields and field art installations
over 50 million mind units were controled over the
*course* of the operation
not to be outdone enlightened agents used the 8th
of August International Cat Day
for launch Operation Felidae and celebrate the cat
as a symbol of the enlightened faction
agents in nineteen cities joined the forces
in the creation of over 20 field art installations and several p8 farms
agents also collected founds for cats shelters
So far sitreps from Chile China the Philippines Russia Scotland
Spain and Sweden have emerged
in July in nagano japan a cross-faction contingent
of 126 agents worked tirelessly to care as several
square mile area of links field and
high-level portals
in order to create a canvas for Operation BlueGreenPlanet
their field art installation was a beautiful
and detailed rendition of planted Earth
agent A B and C have been traveling across Europe
seeking the most powerful XM sources
along their way
in a modified vehicle inspired by the NIA's NL 1331
their journey so far has taken them to
Berlin Dresden Vienna Mannheim and Paris
where they've met with the local
communities
and explore the city's by completing large numbers of missions
on August 1st nearly three thousand agents
in 90 cities participated in agent organized ingress first Saturdays
agent solved puzzles to decrypt postcodes
gained *472* levels and over 300 million AP
as well as walked over 7600 kilometers
nearly the distance from London to Beijing
keep an eye out for information on the next Ingress first
saturday on September 5th
on the 22nd of August agents will be able to
participate in an official mission day in Paris
with curated missions developed
in coordination with the Paris Tourism Authority
this will be an incredible opportunity
to discover hidden gems in the City of Light
RSVP for the event on the ingress Google+ page
agents if you have a sitrep you want to share, intel the
demands our attention
or story you think need to be covered
sharing with us on Google+ and Facebook using the hashtag #ingress
finally I want to share that a
trusted source reached out to me
claiming to have more information about
something called abaddon
the source indicated that this may relate directly
to the origins of the Niantic project
i intend to dig deep into this mystery
I have a feeling I may be headed to Europe
for the Ingress Report I'm susanna Moyar
this is a message for everyone who is watching this
the truth will be uncovered