great things are coming hello agents
I'm she's on a boy and this is the
ingress reports we are just a few days
away from the faster the Persepolis
anomalies
on Saturday 10 2010 agents will converge
on the nominee
site to do battle this place recent
series of anomalies
revolves around and he Magnus leader Joe
Hart and her efforts to reactivate
aging is a technology buried in the
historic passion city of Persepolis
these artifacts about which very little
is night
have lain dormant since the destruction
of the city by Alexander the Great
Johanna allies in the resistance claim
that this technology
can help humanity overcome some if its
greatest ills
including disease hunger and war height
Johnson presents another
the claiming that the Nazi oppose a
great risk to humanity
and is believed to be attempting to
block John's efforts
many are asking how busy it relate to
the shakers
who seem to be the enemy one person who
could shed light on this
its common lanting research and get
thanks but stein lightning
he was recently appeared as an XM entity
within the portal network
just like deborah but don't pitch before
him his fate
is now at stake as the factional
struggle for control of his extension
jobs many agents around the globe have
taken this mission two hearts
in Egypt resistance agent
me likey galarraga near Troy and Gondor
a
travel over 1,700 kilometers by popular
vote
to be ancient city of Luxor to extract
shot number one
with argue both operation ended with the
creation of a 1,200 kilometers
think which transported shot number one
County Arabia
even easier multiple teams the predicted
agent including
sailor Shaman King out the door polygon
and insight 0 helpfully shot number 23
Central Java in an operation that lasted
four days
they were able to fake the fender shown
to be an hour
and later successfully transported shot
number thirteen on the plane reached as
well
in the Philippines attainable United
agent including
chaos 1 known to write a me reports
and storm by coordinated with the team
in Australia
night shot 32 33 before transporting
them
within a funny story with the likely
target taiwan
ultimately capturing both shock in the
Bronx
groups in the united in resistance
agents pleaded in nearly a week
in an attempt to control shot 39 the
resistance ultimately able to extract
the show on
comma in that the american Island over a
hundred agents were involved
including let up you can I is the man
vanass
and me also in front doesn't the
resistance agents from Knotts
including drink 764 X flop
exam 200 and Bryce cap helps safety
sheppard
Shahnameh 22 out of canada and Thailand
in an operation that lasted just over 24
hours
in Romania in light and agents including
standby labs
hyping know that sunshine and encrypted
holeshot number 34
in from ok area and they're protected
net field
they then executed operations offender
shot eat across the black
state catholics Don play joint shot
number 27 currently delight in control
for jean-claude the resistance control
not
however this weekend the target for were
battling the in like a target leave
has learned live with it target will
need to heal
50 at that time the dynamic that this
trouble a change dramatically
last week the enigmatic founder
operation Essex
doctor edgar Allan Wright appeared in
passing on behind the Cana
dont the questions about his of and the
many mysteries surrounding the Niantic
project
as far as it was here you know
and in for past portable past
yeah I consider myself I had never like
yours just
effect and might not sensible I am
subway
I sent our board
cat 30 I have been told that richard
loeb
also known as PA ship I'll will be
appearing on behind the scanner as well
to clarify his role in the creation of a
dead the software
noticed treat Sica you can see behind
the Spanish broadcaster feeding
nobody's will take place this Saturday
in Bratislava and Washington DC
without the like in Columbia sone ki
honoree Phoenix Toronto wanna there is
and on June 28 in Tohoku
you direct important with that slight
tinge a concept had
Liverpool hundred-man helping heat
Milwaukee
Nashville and Paul Collins there will be
no organized activities in Katmandu
and our thoughts are with those working
to rebuild their lives there I will be
in washington DC this Saturday
and I look forward to seeing many of you
there some agents on the ground will be
participating in a series of physically
challenging missions
lead I go back Special Operations
contrary
they will secure information on known
but I'll call calls
I can a lot of time can memoryless that
me back to cited
are in fact the recruitment and training
program can I A
I have also received confirmation that
the second official
ingress mission day will be taking place
in practice law that
Sunday doubling the Persepolis anomaly
designed in partnership with the price
love the Culture and Information Center
it'll be an excellent opportunity
agent with Noel and learn more about
this start them
connecting rest for Saturday will take
place in just over a week on June 6
in over 100 cities around the world find
out more at in West Stockholm flash
events
the ingress reports I'm is an employer
clinton's 18th you are changing rooms
said alt