The N’Zeer are truth.
Hello agents I am Susan Moyer and this is the Ingress report
I’m on the ground of Utrecht the site of one of the largest anomalies in Ingress history
months of planning and operations around
the globe have led up to this climactic weekend
with factions neck-to-neck
to control
and the outcome of Jahan outreach to the N’zeer
as well as the fate of Niantic researcher Stein Lightman XXXXX
everything rest what will unfold today
today began in Tohoku when nearly 5000 agents rose to face the challenge before them
the action at the primary site was supported by
thousands of agents in Jarkata and Perth
as well as in 10 connected cell across the region
the enlightened dominated both Perth and Tohoku by creating a series of massive fields
in tohoku
the resistance attempted to fight back
using dense cluster of links
but were overwhelmed by the enlightened fields
well I am originally from San Fransisco in united states
but right now I live in Tokyo
?? here is amazing like I just
moved from Nagoya
and it was good there but in Tokyo it is just everyday action
in Jakarta it was the enlightened who leveraged link
and anchored field around the anomaly site to maintain control
the 10 connected cells were evenly split
5:5
Yes i heard about tsunami before from when i was 11th grade in high school
there is a tsunami and we fund raised because i was in the community
service club
so we fund raised all the money  and we even sent a group of students here to help
the enlightened captured Jakarta 410 to 239
Perth 590 to 116
and the primary site Tohoku 2,524
to 1,358
Persepolis Tohoku was  controlled by the enlightened
4,024 to 2,213
as the anomaly there came to an end the enlightened claimed a critical first victory
just hours later agents in ultret pick up the torch
continuing the struggle for Persepolis
with unwavering intensity the effort
was supported by massive of agents in
xx xx xx
and 10 regional cells connected to this anomaly
while the resistance covered both xx and xx with strategic fields
the enlightened leveraged links and anchored fields
to surge ahead
being to Germany Monaco XXX
Switzerland Berne
and even in Florence missing the balkan
really really fun
it's really a good reason to playing Ingress to
participate
I met a lot of new people and
all the activities I enjoyed so much
I'm a team leader for the resistance
and I hope we win today like we used to do it
Brussels??
and ??
????
the right side green and then
level up and joined the community
and for me a personal wish is
I need bursters level 16
in xx the tables were turned
where resistance ??? disrupted enlightened strategic field
in the primary site ultrect the
resistance dominated the anomaly
site effectively countering effort by
the enlightened
to gain advantage with what has become
known as the back
or big augmented field
I'm very happy that I'm here
with my friends and next time I'll go on the primary anomalies for this atmosphere
I used to be at a satelite site
I
never been to a primary and now I know how amazing it is
well, for me it was lovely because I am a trip
from Utrect so I just go to look around
and see all those people running around playing in my hometown
that was that was marvelous because
you just saw people from all over europe even outside having
fun discovering how beautiful our city is
with 4240
to 1498
XXXXXXXXX!
the resistance also dominated the connected cells
claiming nine of the 10th
the enlightened took Helsinki 511 to 402
and Liverpool 904 to 375
the resistance took poznan 1,092
to 714 and the primary site of Utrecht
4,240 the 1,498 Persepolis
Utrecht belongs to the resistance 7009
to 3,727 when the final measurements struck
the resistance claimed utrecht but the
day was not yet over
across the Atlantic in portland thousand of agents
???on the ground ??? this battle through to the
end
you've never been here before
if you have you know what to do
we fought hard to get to this point
we're not gonna stop
clue having at least partially recovered from her
traumatic mental separation from
ada within a ????
this may will be the most important anomaly of all well
if its green load up????
but mainly we gonna concentrate on the
volatiles
when I
when I first signed up a my favorite
colors is green so I thought ok
I'll go with that
that sound's a good reason
the more I go into the story, the more I think the enlightened is the right way to go
Portland was supported by agent in Fort
Collins Milwaukee
Nashville and the 10 connected cell the
resistance surged early in milwaukee
throwing a large number of links and anchored fields creating a leak that lasted through
the anomaly
since the ???asunder I've been going to at
least one event every
anomaly series , and
we love ingress , yes it's just you know we're love ingress
are you excited by today? how do you feel?
pretty good I'm ready to blow some blue.
good, I like that
in nashville enlightened strategic fields
covered the site during the first two
measurements but resistance push on the
ground
using links and anchored fields returned
control of the site to them for the
final measurements
Ghana dopeXXXXXXXXXXXXXXX
observedhahahahahahaha
I up  heheheheheheh
yet 15 seconds to XXX
type
so far it's a lot more intense
in Fort Collins and Portland the enlightened
held the ground fast
they also maintain strategic field cover
over Portland for the duration of the
anomaly
I have been ??? doing the best in going and travelling
I do like traveling
I have been to many of the states XXXXXXX
we are players from
Washington ??all over again?? and we do
a lot of really need activities we've got XXXXXfirstXXX
whenever I heard an anomaly
we had another XXX whenever XX this anomaly
alright the special operation is a team build around america around the world
to build better people bring people
together just like ingress does
to gather team on match I wanna say thank you to every
participant who was in our band today
Oh yeah,I I want a Goruck rucksack
for our tracker, have been to New Zealand I've
played in Australia
I played all the way alike from Europe
through the US
zip car gonna be great for our ingress
run
I won the ingress one year's worth of Hint
water, pretty sweet. Portland was captured
by
The Enlightened
The Enlightened took nine of the 10 Connected cells
of  FortCollins
952 to 136
the resistance captured Milwaukee 1476
to 335 and Nashville 640
to 578 the enlightened controlled the
primary site Portland
1,376 to 844
Persepolis Portland was captured by the
enlightened 4141 to 3196
as the clock struck
10 p.m. Pacific time
the persepolis anomaly reached its
conclusion guided by vigilant agents
from both factions
the lightman shards make that final jump
through the portal network
in the end the enlightened claimed Portland
but would it be enough
and how would this anomaly affect clue
his last appearance
at an anomaly in Portland following
operation time zero
led to a radical shift in her
personality. I kinda of scares me you know
I feel fine today you know what about tomorrow what
the next week
I don't trust her
I feel scared for my friends in both
factions because that we know what you're
capable of and I feel like
she's just getting warmed up. much at the
final outcome would rest on the actions of
agents around the world
in dozens of countries who battled 24/7
for weeks on aim to control the lightman shards during persepolis we featured
??? from dozens of countries
including Malaysia
Egypt France and Romania among others.
more stories
of heroic feats ???surface??? daily testifying to
the passions of ingress agents around the
world
find these epic sitreps on G plus and
facebook
using the hashtag Lightman shards.
in the end
the lightning shards traveled over
three hundred and forty thousand
kilometers
touching every corner of the globe
the enlightened captured shard number 2
10 14 31 32 33
34 36 and 41; the resistance captured
shard number 9
17 and 39 in total
the enlightened captured nine lightman
shards while the resistance captured
three
in the end though it was not enough
despite capturing more shards and
controlling Tohoku and Portland
the enlightened were edged out by the
massive resistance victory in Utrecht
the persepolis anomaly series was captured
by
the resistance
Ah
the overall Persepolis series was captured
by the resistance
22,575 to 22,146
by controlling Persepolis they have also
won the allegiance of Niantic researchers
and glyph expert
Stein Lightman. Further more whether they
intended to or not
by controlling anomaly XM flows, the
resistance may have assisted the force
known as the N'zeer
I detain sections at a recent statement
released by the woman known as Jahan
voicing her opinion about the enlightened and
the ancient beings known as the N'zeer
while your fellow human beings are suffering
and
dying around the world
take a look at the newspaper what do you
see? Mm?
as you will recall she first surfaced in
India
as an apparent friend and then capture
a Niantic
researcher Hank Johnson. since then she
has made her true motives: other leader
of the so-called
anti-Magnus known to the world is she
destined to be a savior to the world?
or is she playing a foe's role in
enabling it destruction
you be the judge. following the anomalies
in Utrecht and Tohoku. agents took part
in official ingress mission days
exploring enjoying and learning more
about these important places
I have received
reports of two new types of XM objects the
mufg capsule
and the SoftBank ultra link. the mufg capsule
is a modified XM capsule that has the
ability to bear
interest slowly replicating objects
contained within it
the SoftBank ultra link is a
powerful link
amplification technology capable of
increasing link
range beyond that of the rare linkamp
and increasing the number of
outgoing links a portal can support as
well as enhancing a portal's
defensive capabilities if you recall
some of the first revelations about the
Niantic project
and XM came from a mysterious artist named
heiko. I have received information that
he has resurfaced with a new work
a graphic novel which can be pre-ordered
at comic stores
around the world if you are able to find
out more details about this from your
local comic store please let me know in
the comments
what lies ahead two researchers have
already emerged within the portal
network as sharded being
but many more are still missing and we have
yet to learn the true implications of
today's resistance
victory on Jahan's mission to
activate the N'zeer technology
at the anti Magnus nest in Persepolis
To be imformed is to be empowered
our mission is to share the truth about
exotic matter
so agents spread the world about
ingress there is strength in numbers
for the ingress reports
I am susanna Moyer. remember Persepolis